FROM ME TO YOU 2ND SEASON
So why are you crying?
Is it because of Miura?
S- Sorry.
You felt you had to protect my
feelings. I caused you so much trouble.
I'm sorry. I really am.
- I was trying to be kind.
- Huh?
It's because you're dense!
Huh?
Kazehaya was the one who never felt
sorry for you. In fact, he was the only
one, wasn't he? Even in the beginning of
first year Chizu and Ayane started talking
to you because they pitied you!
Tell me. When you look at
him, what do you even see?!
"What do I...see"?
REACH...
Kuronuma!
So, how goes it? Huh?! Festival prep good?
Yes. Both the costume group and props
group are working hard. It's tight... ...but I
think they'll finish in time. the group
doing fliers is also making good progress.
They'll probably help out the other
groups when they finish up. -Which'll be
nice because the groups that are running
slightly behind could use the help. -'Kay.
I understand?
Then, I have a message for you to give to
those slow groups: "Spare no effort while
you're young. And grab the bull by
its horns!" The situation has changed.
We're gonna kick the 3rd years aside...
and take the grand prize for ourselves!
Top-grade sushi...
- He must have made some kind of bet.
- Oh yeah, by the way...
- I think you totally got the wrong idea.
- Huh?! I did?! Not again!!
I mean Shota isn't even close to the
perfect, impressive guy you think he is!
Soo, it's best you just forget about him!
"Perfect"?
Hello, lowly worker ants! You
putting in that elbow grease?
Oh, look, it's the
worst teacher on the planet.
A total scumbag!
Leeeet's seeeee... looks like all the types
of herbal tea are done and ready to go.
And the café's work
schedules finished. Looks good.
Yano-chin! -How about adding
some herbal ramen to the menu? -No.
Ugh, you are killing me...
Hold on a sec, where's this
part here supposed to go again?
There. See?
- Ah! Okay... brace that side.
- Sure...
But still... I do think he's pretty special.
Uh, by the way, I've been
wondering what those were.
They're references for
the black magic café.
That's some intense stuff,
huh? Be careful with that.
I should just give up? On what?
Going out with Kuronuma?
Or on liking her... at all?
- Whoa, that's a lot of books.
- Looks heavy. What are those?
Oh, they're books on
herbal teas and sweets.
Ah, they're for the black
magic café. Let me look at that.
- But why did you get so many of them?
- Oh... Well, since we're going to call it a
café, I want to make sure our customers
really enjoy their time there.
It'll be super legit then!
Aw, this one's
adorable looks so tasty too!
Yeah? I wanna see! Wow, that is cute!
Oh you think so? I'm so glad!
You always get so overwhelmed
by your own stuff, you know.
It's true. I'm always
just thinking about myself.
I wonder...
When you look at him,
what do you even see?!
Did I start to like Kazehaya...
because I saw him as perfect?
You figured I was cheerful or fair to
everyone. But I was never just "treating
you fairly".
10 DAYS UNTIL SCHOOL FESTIVAL
5 DAYS UNTIL SCHOOL FESTIVAL
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, CHIZU
3 DAYS UNTIL SCHOOL FESTIVAL!!
3 DAYS!!
THE LAST STRETCH!!
HOKKAIDO
BUTTER DROPS
FORTUNE: GREAT LUCK
DAY BEFORE SCHOOL FESTIVAL!
I'm trying to remember what it was... that
made me fall for Kazehaya... in the first
place...
Uhh, Then, without further ado, it's time
for us to begin the 43rd annual Kitahoro
High School Festival.
THE 43RD KITAHORO HIGH SCHOOL FESTIVAL
FESTIVAL TAKOYAKI
GYOZA DUMPLINGS
Come this way for the Fairy Café!
Stop by the Astronomy
Club's mini planetarium!
We do fortune telling!
Iroha karuta reading!
BLACK MAGIC CONSULTATION IN PRACTICE
SADAKO'S BLACK MAGIC CAFÉ
I hate her.
The person I like has a
girlfriend and I absolutely despise her.
I want to make him mine no matter what
I have to do so I need to get rid of her
once and for all.
A-a thinly veiled warning from the
past."Curses, like chickens, come home to
roost."
Now you must prepare yourself to face
the consequences. Therefore, I would say...
W- What's up with these kids? I
feel a toxic aura around them.
Kuronuma's rumors snowballed like crazy,
and it brought in some wild people who're
- kinda into all this stuff...
- Whaaaa? So, this is her?!
Thank you so much! You're right, I'll
face her fair and square! And even if I
- lose, no hard feelings!
- But look. Everybody comes
out all sunshine and rainbows.
A- As expected.
Next person! Go on in!
No, Moe Moe Rock Paper
Scissors is not a thing we do.
Enjoy. Your Shiso tea.
Ah, it smells so wonderful!
What are the
therapeutic effects of this one?
- It's for constipation relief.
- Hiiiiiii!
- Chigusa! Long time no see.
- Do you guys have that
special? Y'know Herbal ramen?
That was rejected.
I'll take this.
The black magic consultation booth
will be going on a 10-minute break now!
The person she liked had a girlfriend...
And not just her. Most of the
customers have love problems.
If Kazehaya didn't already have someone
he liked, would I have ever actually done
something?
And would things be different as a result?
I guess now... I'll never know
Wow, it seems like you've
been working really hard.
Here, my treat.
Did you think that I was Kazehaya?
If Ayane finds out about this, she'll
probably get mad at me again for doing
something "uncalled for".
But I just had to say this.
Can I be honest with you?
To be real... it just seemed impossible...
that you could ever win Kazehaya's heart.
It's obvious you're two different people,
So I didn't see it as a good match. When I
tried to picture who he could go out
with, I never imagined it'd be you.
Plus, it's strange... you told me that you
never felt any distance between the two of
you but from where I was standing it
seemed like there was actually a giant
wall there. It was one you
didn't have with other classmates.
: A distance that's just
between me... and Kazehaya?
But you were way cuter than I expected.
So I kinda thought that... you should give
up on Kazehaya and try to blend into the
class... ...or maybe just
choose someone different.
Iiiii was thinkin'
meeee if you wanted, but...
Sadako... So! Uh...
I thought that you had a nice smile, and
I really wanted to see it some more. That
said, there's only one person who can
make you smile right now. or make you cry
or get all gloomy. Kazehaya, right?
You've got my full
support. So good luck out there.
A wall that's just
between me... and Kazehaya?
I- I'm so sorry.
Thanks a lot!
I started feeling embarrassed
and didn't want him to dislike me.
I couldn't even smile in front of
him... or say what was on my mind.
It makes me wonder if that barrier
between us... that never existed before... was
unconsciously built by me.
When I communicated my thoughts... No
matter what they were... Kazehaya always did
his best to respond to me.
Um, hey... Kazehaya... I'm sorry.
I can see it now Sadako is
just sorta misunderstood.
- I know.
- And I--
Yeah... I think I... was
probably misunderstood.
But... She's been misunderstood so much...
that I can live with her misunderstanding
me.
Still she's always worked
hard without ever giving up.
Yes, it's true. The two of
us are complete opposites.
I get mad. And jealous.
She thinks I'm some amazing guy...
but I just can't live up to that.
I'm not the kind of guy
others should admire.
She always says, I'm the
reason she is who she is today...
But Kuronuma is a force. She works hard
and solves all her problems on her own,
and honestly, I
think... that I admired her.
Well, Kazehaya...
Hey, Kazehaya!
- We came to the famous black magic café!
- We heard the rumors!
That her powers are real!
She really is something
else! Sadako Kuronuma!
Sawako.
It's Sawako Kuronuma.
He kind of felt like a god to me.
He was so bright and cheerful.
- Always the center of attention.
- The black magic café was a big success.
- I looked up to him... and admired him.
- Yeah.
But... the Kazehaya that I found myself
falling in love with... was always just an
ordinary boy.
- Finished! Finally!
- No, we've still got more to
do. The whole costume march.
- Oh! Great! No rest for the weary...
- No beauty sleep...
Sawako!
- Good work!
- Everyone's gonna go home, eat some
dinner, clean up, and then we'll meet back
at my place after!
Heyyyy, have any of
you guys seen Kazehaya?
Uh-uh. Why, did you lose him again,
Joe? Wasn't he just with you guys?
- Kazehaya!
- I don't care.
It doesn't matter.
Huh? That came out of
nowhere. What do you mean?
Wait... D-don't tell me...
It doesn't matter who
Kazehaya likes. I don't care.
Please just go home without me.
Kuronuma, the classroom!
I'm done worrying about what could be.
You won't interfere? That'll be the day.
Being afraid embarrassed...
Stressing over how he might feel about me?
Why did I worry so much?
There are so many
things I want to tell him.
When he's facing away.
His blushing profile.
His face when he panics...
when he gets really angry.
His serious expression. Even his sad one.
And that big bright smile.
If I said I wanted to make all of that
mine, I wonder what kind of face Kazehaya
would show me then.
I'm the one who built this wall between
us... and I'm going to be the one to crush
it! I want him to know.
I hope that my feelings, all of them...
Will reach him.
So please...
Let them reach...]
From me to you!
I like you.
I simply... like you.
Next time: "Confession"